

Kirill Gorbachyonok

iOS Engineer

GitHub LinkedIn Telegram **Email**



About Me

I'm developer and kind of designer. Love to learn new stuff in programming and optimising my life with that knowledge. Specialising on iOS and macOS development. My goal is to become a brilliant specialist in software engineering and make someone's life a little bit easier with the help of software I make. Also love to pet my imaginary cat.



Education

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

2017 - 2021

Bachelor degree

Currently I'm a 4th year student of BSUIR. Here I'm specializing on Informatics and Programming Technologies.



Languages

English: Upper Intermediate

Russian: Native speaker Belarusian: Native speaker

Experience

EduDo

September 2020 - ...

About: mobile learning platform with short user-generated interactive videos. Winner of category **Mobile App of the Year 2020 on Product Hunt**.

Role: One of the core engineers of iOS application. Me and my colleague developed application from scratch to production ready state for 3 months.

- Self education in development for Apple platforms December 2019 - August 2020
- iOS trainee in iTechArt October 2019 - November 2019
- Enter as first year student in BSUIR September 2017



ু Skills

I'm in love with open source community and try to contribute back by developing applications and utilities. All my work you can find in my <u>GitHub profile</u>. Here a list of projects that I'm most proud of:

• PhotoMap * iOS, Swift

PhotoMap is an application which allows to make and organise photos on the map.

• TaskManager * macOS, Swift

View OS running processes and plots of how system resources are managed. Implemented in SwiftUI.

• **DEKit** * macOS/Linux, Swift

Directory Events Kit is a library design to simply notify when something happens in directory.

• **UDPChat** * macOS, Swift

CLI chat based on UDP sockets.

• **Dotfiles** * macOS, Bash

My current macOS setup. Here I share my zsh config with aliases and functions to work more efficiently in Terminal, my applications with their setups. Also here you can find some cron jobs to automate your life.